ANTOINETTE M. MASCARELLO

Full Stack Web Developer, Designer, and Content Creator



CONTACT

Orlando, FL 407 - 962 - 6635 antoinette.mascarello@gmail.com www.amascarello.com www.linkedin.com/in/mascarelloa www.github.com/mascarelloa



EDUCATION

Web Development, Certificate

University of Central Florida | Completed June 2021

Writing and Rhetoric, B.A.

University of Central Florida | Completed December 2019



SUMMARY

I am a detail oriented, fast learning full stack web developer and designer with excellent written and verbal communication skills, problem solving capabilities, and a strong work ethic. I specialize in creating user-friendly and responsive applications, graphic art, and content.



WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

Ecsazza Inc. (Washington, D.C.) | August 2021 to Present Responsibilities: Developing, analyzing and maintaining software applications, designing scalable, testable code, fixing programming bugs for a startup Software-as-a-Service provider.

Freelance Web Developer and Graphic Designer

Self-employed (Orlando, FL.) | March 2021 to Present Responsibilities: Designing, coding, and deploying single page brochure pages, logos, and print materials for clients.

Recruitment Specialist

NXTThing RPO (Columbus, OH.) | August 2021 to Present Responsibilities: Conducting preliminary interviews with prospective candidates, sending employment offers, and updating appropriate portals with new hire information.



SKILLS

Languages & Frameworks

HTML5, CSS3, Sass, JavaScript (ES6+), React, jQuery, Node, Express, MySQL, MongoDB, Bootstrap

Tools & Software

Git/Version Control, Atlassian, GitHub, Bitbucket, Firebase, Heroku, Microsoft Office, Google Suite, Adobe XD, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe InDesign, Adobe Illustrator, Wordpress

Industry Knowledge

UX/UI Design, Responsive Web Design, Object Oriented Programming, MVC, Web APIs, Agile Environments, Graphic Design, SEO Optimization



RECENT PROJECTS

Knowsy

Built with React, Node, Express, MongoDB, CSS. Description: An app that allows users to take and create categorized quizzes for fun or for study purposes and view quiz stats on a personal dashboard. View repository at https://github.com/mascarelloa/knowsy

Astroscope

Built with HTML, CSS, JavaScript.

Description: An app that allows users to take and create categorized quizzes for fun or for study purposes and view quiz stats on a personal dashboard. View repository at https://github.com/mascarelloa/astroscope